Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XLVIII is arranged in 26 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XLVIII. BROTHERHOOD BANK
  - Sub-Series 309-0. Brotherhood Bank
    - General, 1928 (Box 495, Folder 19)
    - General, 1933-1934 (Box 495, Folder 20)
    - General, 1932 (Box 495, Folder 21)
    - General, 1930 (Box 495, Folder 22)
    - General (Box 495, Folder 23)
      not dated.
    - General, 1928-1929 (Box 495, Folder 24)
    - General, 1926-1927 (Box 495, Folder 25)
    - General, 1926 (Box 495, Folder 26)
    - General, 1924 (Box 495, Folder 27)
    - General, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 28)
    - General, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 309-3. Brotherhood Bank
    - Application for Employment, 1927 (Box 495, Folder 30)
    - Application for Employment, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 31)
    - Application for Employment, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 309-5. Brotherhood Bank
    - Extension of Charter, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 33-34)
  - Sub-Series 309-6. Brotherhood Bank
    - Stock, 1928-1929 (Box 495, Folder 35)
    - Stock, 1924 (Box 495, Folder 36)
    - Stock, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 309-8. Brotherhood Bank
    - Correspondents, 1924 (Box 495, Folder 38)
    - Correspondents, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 309-9. Brotherhood Bank
    - Furniture and Fixtures, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 40)
    - Furniture and Fixtures, 1924 (Box 495, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 309-10. Brotherhood Bank
    - Accounts, 1930 (Box 495, Folder 42)
    - Accounts, 1929 (Box 495, Folder 43)
    - Accounts, 1927 (Box 495, Folder 44)
    - Accounts, 1926 (Box 495, Folder 45)
    - Accounts, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 46)
    - Accounts, 1924 (Box 495, Folder 47)
    - Accounts, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 309-11. Brotherhood Bank
    - Burglary and Robbery Insurance, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 309-12. Brotherhood Bank
    - Advertising, 1929 (Box 495, Folder 50)
    - Advertising, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 51)
    - Advertising, 1923-1924 (Box 495, Folder 52)
    - Advertising, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 309-13. Brotherhood Bank
    - Opening, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 309-14. Brotherhood Bank
    - Personnel, 1930 (Box 495, Folder 55)
    - Personnel, 1929 (Box 495, Folder 56)
    - Personnel, 1926 (Box 495, Folder 57)
    - Personnel, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 309-15. Brotherhood Bank
    - Depositories, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 309-16. Brotherhood Bank
    - Loans, 1931 (Box 495, Folder 60)
    - Loans, 1930 (Box 495, Folder 61)
    - Loans, 1927 (Box 495, Folder 62)
    - Loans, 1926 (Box 495, Folder 63)
    - Loans, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 64)
    - Loans, 1924 (Box 495, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 309-17. Brotherhood Bank
    - Bills, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 309-18. Brotherhood Bank
    - Request for Bank Currency, 1924 (Box 495, Folder 67)
    - Request for Bank Currency, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 309-19. Brotherhood Bank
    - Annual Meeting of Shareholders, 1936 (Box 495, Folder 69)
    - Annual Meeting of Shareholders, 1930 (Box 495, Folder 70)
    - Annual Meeting of Shareholders, 1929 (Box 495, Folder 71)
    - Annual Meeting of Shareholders, 1926 (Box 495, Folder 72)
    - Annual Meeting of Shareholders, 1924 (Box 495, Folder 73)
    - Annual Meeting of Shareholders, 1923 (Box 495, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 309-20. Brotherhood Bank
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1933-1943 (Box 495, Folder 75)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1926 (Box 495, Folder 76)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 77)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1926 (Box 495, Folder 78)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1924 (Box 495, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 309-21. Brotherhood Bank
    - Meeting of Committee, 1927 (Box 495, Folder 80)
    - Meeting of Committee, 1926 (Box 495, Folder 81)
    - Meeting of Committee, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 309-22. Brotherhood Bank
    - Membership Loan Plan, 1927 (Box 495, Folder 83)
    - Membership Loan Plan, 1925 (Box 495, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 309-23. Brotherhood Bank
    - Dividends, 1926-1927 (Box 495, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 309-24. Brotherhood Bank
    - Claim Against Rylee, C.E., 1927 (Box 495, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 309-25. Brotherhood Bank
    - Information on China, 1927 (Box 495, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 309-26. Brotherhood Bank
    - Change of Name, 1927 (Box 495, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 309-27. Brotherhood Bank
    - Increased Capitalization, 1929 (Box 495, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 309-28. Brotherhood Bank
    - Suspension of Payment. Newspaper Clippings, 1931 (Box 495, Folder 90)
    - Suspension of Payment. Correspondence and Newspaper Clippings, 1930 (Box 495, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 309-29. Brotherhood Bank
    - Sale of Bank, 1934 (Box 495, Folder 92)
    - Sale of Bank, 1930 (Box 495, Folder 93)
    - Sale of Bank. Liquidating Committee, 1930-1943 (Box 495, Folder 94)
    - Sale of Bank. Newspaper Clippings, 1930 (Box 495, Folder 95)